okay we're just going to get this all out of the way just in case we do take
your case but I'm just not sure about taking your place because we can
discuss why in a second today is 1 2 18
that's what happened on January 1 1 1 wow how bring in the new year that's not
good I know I said a red light waiting to turn to the furthest onto the furthest
left lane okay so you're not in the inner lane or in the outer lane outer
left lane and you're stuck okay but you're in the turn lane okay and then
there was another car coming so you are showing me from let me show you if
you're the white car you're waiting I see this black car and the black
car is coming and I'm looking at it and I'm thinking oh my god he's really
going to pass even though traffic going through and as he was going through it
was clear up until a car came and they hit the car went that way and it's
me okay so it's that black car okay got it
Yukon so there's five cars right yeah there's a Yukon right next to me
okay okay and the car behind me so let's look we're more cars okay so then this
is the car that's coming this way yeah okay so there's a car behind me
they Yukon work on the side of me so this guy hits and then they ricochet like
that you and this guy yes which is right in the middle and then it felt his
back kind of like this at an angle so it's wedged in between this like that
okay got it I have gotten it I understand you're in the furthest you're in the
inner lane where there's a car next to you or no there was no car next to me but
there was a lane next to you though there is there's an empty lane nobody was here okay got it
I was here there was nobody right there in which street is it that you're on
I'm not really watching the streets was Washington Washington and your head
towards sunrise mountain or red rock sunrise mountain okay Washington
Washington
and there's that guy the Yukon was in a straight lane right yes
the car is that green one do you remember um it was a green one I'm not sure if it was
like a corona or a Toyota it was smashed as well I couldn't really tell and the one
that ran the red light was the black car I don't even know what car that was as
but everyone knows it says fault right everyone says it was this guy's fault right yeah okay
because it was evading police evading police yeah
that didn't work out no
did you get any other insult from the black car um the only thing that I figured out was that it
was a lift driver who um I guess it was a rental from lift or something and um they're maybe
mistaken the hospital and it's jail she was driving for a lift was the app on
I have no idea the only thing that this only was that it was a bit
driver but they say it was a rental it was a rental that the insurance company
supposed to be for all the damages or whatever she was
when I insurance you know that's what the police do
okay
You still have, she took it.
Is your Easter and was the cross street?
Yes, Easter and was…
You're an Eastern was the cross street?
You did.
Eastern was.
Okay, let me picture.
Okay, so...
Um...
We're going to need your insurance declaration page.
Do you have pictures of accident?
Okay.
I know where it's located.
And make me a case monitor.
Okay, so...
You do have pictures you said?
Yes.
Okay, good.
Don't worry about it right now.
Okay.
No, no, no, we're good.
Um...
Um, I didn't.
No hospital bill.
Okay.
No worries.
I didn't feel hurt enough to go to the hospital.
Surprised at that all the time.
Where's the car now?
Um, the car is in the tollot.
I gave that information as well on the vehicle.
I don't have the car.
Um, there was a gentleman who referred me to this place.
Okay, we do need your VIN number.
Is this it?
Yes.
The Honda Accord.
Number?
Okay.
And where's the tow yard?
It is right here, 22 and 1 North Congress.
Surprised.
Yeah, it comes when you sign up for it or when you...
It's okay.
When you file the report.
Is there any way you can take a picture of that?
Yeah, yeah.
Take a picture of it.
Ensure what it looks like.
Okay.
You know that stuff though.
And ask them to call you and brothers.
Thanks.
Okay.
Getting the information here.
Do you think the car is going to be totaled or do you think it is?
Yeah, they told me what the engine was on.
The police and the transmission zone.
And the back was smashed as well.
Because it kind of bounced back.
And it hit the car and back up me.
What is trash too?
The back of the trunk of the car.
It was also smashed in.
What?
It was going on in this guy's head.
Girl.
Yeah.
Girl's head.
I couldn't believe it.
I thought it was a dude.
I was like, what's going on?
I felt my first initial thought.
I was like, I thought it was a dude.
Okay.
So how many people were in your vehicle?
Me and my baby.
You and your baby.
Baby seems okay, right?
Yeah.
Mostly that night was like a really rough night.
He like would not speak at all.
He was screaming the whole entire night.
And I'm pretty sure it's from the same scare.
He does have like these marks right here, of course,
from the seatbelt.
And they're like all around his neck.
There really little blood.
I'm not sure what they're called.
Like laceration marks?
Yeah.
Okay.
If you want to take him to be seen, there is a place.
And I'll give you that info.
Okay.
It's a green valley, something,
unless you have a pediatrician, you know,
that you can get him seen it.
My pediatrician, I can get him seen there,
but if you'd better recommend it.
Okay.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Whichever one can get you in sooner.
Okay.
I'm sure they can get you in sooner,
but wherever, you know.
Okay.
So let's talk about babies.
Miners.
Let's talk about people and vehicles,
and claimants,
and let's talk about, uh,
lift.
Let's talk about the toe.
So I'm going to write down my notes here.
I bring things like this.
It's awesome.
You have to write down.
There I go.
Yeah.
So I don't forget anything.
Okay.
What is this?
Isela?
Isela.
Yes.
That's true.
Uh, two B-U-T-E.
At gmail.com.
Okay.
Any other witnesses to the events
that were standing nearby right here?
Right.
Yes.
And I know all the other people in the cars were
kind of the way they were up.
And I know the people in the UConn were also up.
It also has the same police report.
I know the same plenty of people spoke to them as well.
The photo's pretty much took everybody's cars.
Okay.
No worries.
I have to get in on this to the people.
That was a jingle.
And I'm looking behind the UConn.
What is your oh there was what a gentleman that was just part like waiting with him
But he wasn't involved in it. He was like I know you can't see
Okay, but none that you got like no on the side of the street or anything. Okay
Oh
Wow, that's a lot of issues
You've never had any prior accidents or any of that. I know him
Okay, so what is your child's name?
I've been I also put it in one of the drivers, but I kind of the person
Oh, okay the Sarah
I'm gonna take this
You can break that too
I need a second
Thank you
Okay.
See if I have read you read all this.
Five vehicles.
How many people were in?
The woman that was driving the defendant hers.
The black one?
It was just her.
How many people in the gray car?
I'm not too sure about that.
I don't even know.
Okay.
How many people in the car behind you?
There was one man.
What car was that?
It was a white car as well.
I don't even know.
Okay.
How many were in the Yukon?
The Yukon was quite a bit.
Maybe like three of those.
Three children?
I don't even know.
He does sound loud right now.
Can't be if there is no too many people doing well.
Yeah, I was going to leave back from the doctor's office.
And the joy has been...
He was sick.
Okay.
So you're going home?
Going back to this.
over Toyota. Was that the great car? I believe that was the one right here in the middle of us.
Okay, yeah. Got it. Tahoe?
Got it, got it.
Okay, back to this.
So, do you live in like an H.O.A. community?
Um, where do you guys live?
Um, we live in a house in North Las Vegas.
And there's no H.O.A.? No, H.O.A.
Yes.
Can you be more clear on what that means?
Is it like the government phase you rent? No.
Um, an H.O.A. is like, uh, rules and regulations of the community.
Oh, no. So, some people live in a community where it's like, don't park your car outside,
don't paint your house unless you ask us what color.
Yeah. And they pay a monthly fee for that?
No. Okay, so if you don't live in H.O.A.
community, I would suggest getting the car towed to where you are.
Okay. Just because I don't want to tow it there and then you incur all these fees
because H.O.A. is finding you because you're an office at the cars park there.
But if it's going to be towed, um,
no, let me finish this part here.
Let me know it's here. Okay. Um, if it's going to be towed,
so what they normally do is they look at the blue book value of your car.
So they'll say 2003 Honda or whatever you have.
Okay. Um, is that what you have?
2008 Honda.
Okay. So let's say you have a 2008 Honda and they're going to look at it and say 2008 Honda,
I think I have a 2006 Honda.
Good? Yeah, I have a 2006 Honda.
And I don't even know what my car's worth.
But let's say it's worth five grand.
Okay. They're going to say, well, her 2008's worth six grand.
And because we looked it up on Kelly Blue Book.
And then they're going to give you the Kelly Blue Book version of what your car would be.
Hopefully, unless they try to cheapen it down somehow.
Okay. So I would go on to Kelly Blue Book and look up yours.
Because you're the one that knows your car best.
I can't go enter in if it's got, you know, a moonroof or,
or, you know, some kind of cool little stereo system or something.
And then if there was anything that you fixed on the car recently,
like, hey, I put in a whole new transmission in like a month ago.
And here's my thousand dollar, you know, receipt.
Then you would bring that up now.
Okay. Or like I souped it up and I've got like the subwoofer from all subwoofers.
You know? No.
You think you never fixed it, right?
Yeah. Nope.
I used to be like that in school.
I don't know if it was, I haven't had an accident forever.
You know what I mean? But like when I was in school,
I'd be like, I'm just not going to fix it because someone's going to hit the back of it.
Never mind.
Yeah, it's just, just give it a second.
It'll just, you know, maybe it was because I was a bad driver, you know?
Okay, where is it that you live near?
I live close by the decor casino.
I don't know what that is.
So it's going to rain and let's take a little over there.
It's going to be like cherry and succinct.
Yeah.
It's like a city center.
It's like the city center.
Stake is Boulevard.
Carey.
City center right here.
8900.
Correct.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
Go ahead.
Do it.
You don't really work then?
No. So can we make your appointments whenever or do you prefer a certain time?
I prefer the morning time only because right now if that was my only transportation, so my
mom's basically going to be using me right now.
You missed your mother. Like you mother.
I think boomerang children, they come back.
I know, yeah. She has sticks.
I'll just imagine.
All of them will be molded.
Okay, I'm not.
I'm just going to make one.
I think that's um, you can pick it up.
It's not L.S. It's not a little bit exciting or...
You prefer mornings?
Take home.
It's your mine.
Oh, that's yours.
If you get an estimate of your vehicle, make sure you give us a copy.
Okay, awesome.
So I'm going to put that on your homework.
I just kind of got lost a little bit.
Who gets the estimate?
So they may give you something in the mail when they total out your car.
It depends on what kind of insurance your your aunt has.
Okay.
So we will talk about that too.
Let me add that to my list.
Should we have a comparison?
Oh.
So that's not good.
Who else do you live with?
I'm just my mother-in-law.
Does fiance or mother-in-law have health car insurance?
Health car insurance?
No, just car insurance.
That's her vehicle.
The mother-in-law is the vehicle owner.
Okay, hold on.
I'm sorry.
She's kind of like an aunt then.
No.
She's your mother-in-law.
Oh, I thought it was your aunt that owned the vehicle.
No.
I put mother-in-law.
Okay.
Hearing things.
It's okay.
But the fiance has no health car insurance.
No.
The only car that you guys had was this one.
And it's all her house liability.
Okay.
We have cancer.
So I'm the one dragging her places.
I'm taking her through doctor appointments.
I'm taking her to blood work.
I'm doing what I do.
And that's the car that we have on the lane.
And it's really messed up then.
Because the lady decided to do something stupid
that we don't have to suffer for it.
Life.
Yeah.
Okay.
So we're going to give you a text line.
Let's see how it goes down on that.
How's it going over here?
Yeah.
Okay.
We're going to give you a number.
And you can text all those pictures.
And everything that you have,
ID's and license.
Okay.
We're going to give you a number.
And you can text all those pictures.
And everything that you have,
ID's and license plates and stuff too.
It's just a text line.
If you want to make calls,
you need to call the office.
Because people will call that number.
And you can't pick up from that number.
It's just for texting.
Okay.
So when you text to you,
like, text first,
who you are,
and then text first.
Yeah.
Who will.
So that means,
yeah, it's a text line.
And it's not like a normal text line.
You can see it right away.
But sometimes we see it like,
it only sends it to us like,
during like 7 a.m. and 7 p.m.
So we're not like every day.
Like, I was doing something.
I was doing something.
You know what I mean?
So it doesn't distract us.
You know?
So some people are like,
hey, why have you answered my text?
Because I only see it in certain periods of time.
So if you have any emergencies,
just call the office.
Okay.
You can speak to the gesture
about the accident or your injuries.
Because the gestures are not your friends.
Okay, ever go to court.
They are sitting there on the other side,
trying to make you lose your case.
Okay.
So if you can talk to them about your car,
like, hey, when you're going to fix my car,
when you're giving them money from my car,
when you do a little bit of car,
they don't tell them about your accident or your injuries,
because they're going to try and trick you,
into saying something that later on,
you'll be like,
we got you on recording,
and you said this.
Okay.
Well, two days later,
like I was throwing up and all this other stuff,
and I didn't tell you that,
because that was two days later.
You know what I mean?
So you never ever want to talk to insurance companies,
even if it's your own insurance company most of the time.
Okay.
You are going to need to open up the claim with lift,
because we've tried opening up claims with them,
and they won't talk to us.
So you can talk to them,
open up the claim,
don't tell them about the accident,
don't tell them about your injuries,
and then just say,
hey, speak to my attorney about that.
You can open the claim with lift.
Okay.
So you can just kind of call them,
like, on a different...
There's a...
I'll text you the website,
and you, like, enter in your info,
like, hey, I wasn't involved in an accident,
on January 1st, at 2 p.m.,
or whatever,
and here's my phone number,
and they'll call you back.
Okay.
And after that, I just gave them your information,
or is it right now?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll just tell them about the car,
property damage only.
If you need to talk to me about injuries,
or the accident, call my client,
call my attorney,
I'll authorize you to speak to my attorney.
Okay.
Um...
Let's see.
So...
Uh...
And I would do that as soon as possible,
because you want to see if lift has coverage.
Okay.
That's the...
Today, basically.
Yeah.
Where did it go?
Where's your...
To-do list.
Okay.
Yeah.
She's going to need one.
That would be great.
Yeah.
Oh.
We've got your to-do list.
Okay.
We're going to need your vehicle towed,
because, um...
I'm going to go back to that.
Sorry.
Because when they look at the car damage,
they will take out the money that it's been in the tow yard.
Because the tow yard charge is like $250, $300, $500 a day.
So let's say that they think your car's worth $6 grand,
they'll be like, well, it was there for three days,
so we're going to take off a brand.
So now you only have $5 grand,
because it's too bad, so sad you should take in your car out.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
So we're going to give that thing,
take it out as soon as possible.
So that's why we're getting it towed to your place.
So how do we do that?
Do we just get a tow company and just get it,
or...
Yeah.
Because you only have liability.
Unfortunately, in the United States,
it's kind of like innocent, so proving guilty.
So you have to do all this stuff,
and then hope that the other party has enough money to reimburse you.
Okay.
So now let's talk to you about lift and everything.
So in Nevada, the laws with lift are such that
if you have the app on,
and you've got passengers, you've got 1.5 million worth of coverage.
If you have the app on,
and you don't have any passengers on in the car,
you've got $50 grand.
So you're hoping that she has the app on,
and no people in the car.
Yeah.
Okay, because there's no people in the car,
so she'll have the app on.
Yeah.
If she doesn't have the app on, it's 15 grand.
Okay.
So what happens if there was a rental?
Rental is the minimum, state minimum, 15.
So rental coverage is,
you can pull the coverage to see if there is anything.
So when you go to the store and you go rent a car,
you can say, hey, I want extra coverage,
and I'll pay for the 1.5 million extra, right?
I'll pay the extra 20 bucks a day to get that car insurance out
that this person did that.
Yeah.
Okay, so she probably said,
I just want to rent, and I want to Uber today,
and I'm just not going to pay for that extra insurance.
So it is whatever insurance she has,
which is probably 15 grand,
because people that are rational and stuff
don't really run red lights and try to escape the police.
Exactly.
Okay.
So best case scenario,
you've got 50 grand for this accident.
Worst case scenario, you've got 15.
Okay.
Split amongst everyone.
Wow.
And $10,000 for car damage.
Split amongst everyone.
Wow.
So you guys may be out of car,
and you may have to start looking for a car.
And saving for a car.
It is true.
But this is where you have to get extra coverages.
Come on.
Six.
So this is where it lies.
The issue is,
we don't know what kind of coverage she has,
so hopefully she has the lift app on.
So if you have the app on,
and you're like going off to pick someone up,
then it's 50 grand of coverage.
But even then,
it's not pretty much not that great,
because,
it's not that great,
because there are five vehicles.
Correct.
And there's at least,
let's say there's just six people in the Yukon.
One of them being a third vehicle,
I know that the cops will be,
they're not going to cover her vehicle.
They're never going to cover her.
Unless she had a passenger.
So the other four vehicles,
but you've got you and him,
if he treats.
That's two claimants within a half.
The lady in the car that went to the ambulance,
so her medical bills are higher than yours already.
And anyone in her vehicle,
so let's assume it's just one.
The person behind you and the man in the white car,
that's three.
So now we're three and a half.
And the other car had three,
six to seven people in there.
So now we're looking at 10 people.
Even at 50 grand,
just split amongst 10.
That's not very much.
Makes sense?
See why I cannot,
probably can't take the case.
I'll help you out,
but I probably won't be able to take the case.
Okay?
So we'll help you out a little bit with it,
and your property damage and everything,
but I just don't see this being a case that we can take.
If it was great,
if your aunt had that coverage,
but you just told me she's...
She's liability.
Yeah, liability.
So now you know what to do when you're in an accident,
you get...
If it's a car,
if you don't mind,
like my mom has an old car,
an old beater,
like, you know,
she's probably digging it into,
like, several things,
15 times already.
It's only worth three grand,
you know what I mean?
I'm not going to go insure it for full coverage.
Yeah.
Makes sense?
I'm going to do only liability on that one,
but I'm going to buy extra coverage for me,
because you can always buy extra coverage for you,
because you don't know how someone else is driving.
Okay.
So yeah, I don't think that your car is going to be covered.
You're probably going to have to buy any car.
I'm just telling you,
yeah, based on the facts,
there's 50,000 for 10 people.
Um, rental car coverage.
If you don't have rental car coverage on your thing,
you're probably not going to get rental car coverage.
And I think you said you don't have liability,
so you doubtfully have rental car coverage.
You may want to get that next time you get a vehicle.
All these things that you need to do,
when you get insurance next time,
just like,
you've already taken a picture of it.
Yes.
So I would get that kind of coverage.
And I know money is tight
with your mother-in-law having cancer and everything.
Um, okay.
Other than that.
Yeah.
Do you have health insurance?
Yes.
You do have to,
what is it like Medicare and Medicaid?
Oh, Medicaid.
Medicaid.
Do you have a copy of that?
Can you make a copy of it?
I believe I did.
Oh, you did?
Okay.
So you might want to treat under Medicaid
until, you know, if there's coverage,
even if there is coverage.
It's not going to be enough to have a case over.
Yeah.
You know, if you have coverage,
you turn out that it's a lift vehicle, call me,
and I'll show you how to do this claim on your own.
Okay.
We'll talk about it then.
Um, just, but you need to make sure
that you treat consistently.
Okay.
Otherwise, if, even,
whether or not,
let's say you treat consistently on Medicare
or Medicare or whatever,
until you realize whether or not they have that lift open or not.
Okay.
Because if you don't treat consistently,
you're going to say you're not hurt,
I'm not giving you anything.
Like, I have clients that, like, do it on their own,
and then they text me after the fact,
when you open stuff, they find us.
And they're like, oh, well, I decide to go,
and then I got side track with work,
and then I didn't go,
and then now they're not paying anything.
I'm like, yeah.
You know, because if you were injured,
you would have gone to see them, you know,
you have to go not like every other freaking two, three months, right?
Because then they'll be like,
you must hurt yourself,
zoom by, or something.
Okay.
Tell the doctors everything that hurts the first,
otherwise they will not cover it.
Okay.
And that is basically it.
Let's see.
We're in the vehicle towed out.
The police report takes 10 to 15 days to get.
And then if you need to call us,
just call us, text us or email us,
and we'll be available, okay?
Okay.
And yeah, just don't drop by, make an appointment.
That's basically it.
Do you have any questions?
No.
Okay.
Can't support me that can't support me.